Hey, uh-uh.
Aah!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
Two minutes.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Wow.
It's not hitting at all.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Hello everyone. Hello. I'm Inagi Inoue.
I'm Inagi Inoue. - I'm Kaori Kakihara.
Yes, we're here at the glittering place.
We're so gorgeous!
We're here.
This is a facility where you can experience attractions.
It's a collaboration with an anime.
That's right.
We both like anime.
Yes.
And the anime is...
We are currently collaborating with an anime called "Sword Art Online".
I love Sword Art Online so much.
I'm so happy to have been invited.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I wonder what it's like to collaborate with a game.
It's true.
Yes, it is.
It might be a little difficult.
According to the information I just heard, the clear rate is 1%.
Oh no!
What are we going to do?
What to do?
Since the real Sword Art Online anime
It's about the world in the game.
Oh, really?
What's more...
If you die in the game, you die in the real world too.
in the real world as well.
Then we won't die by ourselves.
That's a no-no.
It's a death match.
I've heard of it, but I don't know much about it.
I don't know much about it.
But it seems like it's something anyone can enjoy.
Let's have fun together!
Ah!
Hey, Naki, you like this anime a lot, don't you?
Yes, it's the anime that made me fall in love with anime.
Oh, really?
The worldview is great, and the characters are really cute.
There are lots of cute girls.
I see.
I love it.
Who's your favorite character?
I really can't decide.
There are so many.
There are so many, but my eternal favorite is Asuna.
Heroine.
The heroine.
Asuna, the heroine.
She's strong, cool and pretty. I'm growing my hair long to be like her.
I'm growing my hair long.
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
Yes. Yes.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
I can't get enough of it!
I wonder if they'll come out...
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to entering that world in my dreams.
Dreams are amazing!
I'm looking forward to it.
Hey, how's it going?
That's great!
This is not where we're going
I'm telling you.
Obviously laughing
It's a great fight!
Oh, wow.
He's so cute!
It's true.
I'm going to buy it.
I'm going to get some.
I'll go get some.
Goods
Let's find some
Let's find some.
Oh, my gosh!
I want to shake your hand.
Kirito and Asuna are wearing different outfits.
It's true... All of them.
There's mail and stuff.
Amazing.
He's turning into a nerd.
He's so cute!
I'm gonna go for it.
He's so cute.
He's cute.
I'm not going to give it my best shot.
Oh, shit.
What's going on?
Something's jamming the scene.
Wait, it's counting down.
It's our gimmick troupe.
Oh, that's right.
I mixed Asuna's group with ours.
What?
Yes...
Yes
Yes.
eh?
something
It's like this way already.
Thank you very much
Let's go to the Gimmeidan and walk...
Ah!
May I come in?
How did you do that?
Oh, here.
Forty seconds.
I'm in.
Oh, is this it?
I just need to touch it.
Touch it.
Here.
I thought I was supposed to touch the device.
Oh, my God.
100% in 30 seconds.
He's so cute.
Who's this?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That's cool.
Oh, wow.Oh, wow.
Looks like Kirito-kun.
He's so cute!
What's this?
Wait, everyone, it's done!
Oh, the link mat!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God.
That's really great.
Lynx Matt.
It's a virtual MMO.
Cool.
Oh, there's Yui!
Hey, Yui.
I'm in.
Is this it?
Here.
I'm in.
Here you go.
Wow.
eh?
Uh...
Which way? Which way?
Is it this way?
Oh, wow!
So cool!
He said, "What?
I didn't hear anything.
He said, "Oh," he said, "Oh," he said.
Okay, let's go.
Let's do it.
Oh, wow.
Oh, this.
Wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
There's a name.
Oh, here.
Here we go.
Oh, my God!
That's great!
Cool!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, man! It didn't work at all!
Oh, my God!
Oh, that's it!
Is it starting?
What?
Where is it?
Oh, no!
When?
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
It won't shut off!
It won't cut! It won't cut!
It won't cut!
Hold on!
Oh, no!
It's coming so fast! It's coming so fast!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
I'm scared! Scary! I'm scared!
Three times?
What? Wait a minute!
What do you mean? What do you mean?
Wow!
Yay!
Yeah!
Wow!
Tension!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
That's great! It's clear! I did it! It's fun! It's so much fun! That's great! You did it! All right! Let's go! Yes!
Let's go!
We'll get the map to get it.
Yes, sir.
You need to complete the combination of the three disparate maps.
Yup.
Let's start looking for it.
Yes, sir.
Green 436270.
436270.
Is it this way?
It's green, right?
436270.
Green!
But I don't know. Can we get through here?
What?
We're going through here?
Oh, no!
Oh, my God!
Wow!
That means it's green that way.
Okay, let's go.
Can you make it?
Yeah!
Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
Oh, my God!
436270.
Aah! Oh, my God! Here!
Wow!
Oh, my God!
Wow! Oh, my God!
Blue! Did you find it?
Oh!
Blue hub
Blue terminal
Teams should expect something for each item
96,000 to $9,800
98,000 yen
Just touch the numbers 96000 to 98000 yen
Then from the blue.
From the blue.
This is hard. This is hard.
I'm a little confused.
We're in the blue area.
Here we go.
Oh! That's it!
Red tablet 108.
Butter.
Red, red, red.
I'm not listening to you!
I'm not listening to you.
I can't do 4x49.
It's a little difficult.
Was it 108?
It was 108.
Oh, my God.
80. - Oh, my God.
I think it was 108
No, it wasn't.
Oh, my God.
We can't do arithmetic anymore.
We can't do math.
Not this one.
That's it!
If we add them together, we get...
It's here, isn't it?
I don't see anything.
155.
What is it?What is it?
Hey...
8×16 is different here, isn't it?
Definitely not.
Ten-eight.
No, it's not.
Did I look here?
Did you look here?
No, I didn't.
I didn't see it.
You didn't see this?
That's...
I didn't look here.
That one.
That one and that one.
That's this one.
Oh, shit.
Got it.
There it is.
Course.
Just a little bit.
This one's stuck.
Watch out!
All right, let's do it.
Here you go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Ora!
You will need to complete the three rooms indicated on the story map.
You can go on to the next one.
But please wait two more minutes.
Beep, beep.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Go-go.
Thank you.
It says "No Trespassing.
Oh, no.
You can't do that.
What did you do?
Oh, no.
Akari's here.
Wait a minute.
Help!
Help me!
Ahhh...
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Hey...
Hang in there.
Nein nein nein.
Negative, negative, negative.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What are you talking about?
Smile?
I'm good at that, guys.
You'd like it if they sang this to you?
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, is it ready?
The guy's peripheral's up.
All I'm getting is the girl's voice.
Is it going up?
Up, up, up.
Go, go, go, go.
Smile. Smile.
Smile.
I'm having fun.
That was good!
I got it!
Isn't it kinda white?
Next item I got was a game closer!
Really?
My shoulder?
Wow! Wow!
I really got the screen when I got the item in the game... now!
Wow!
Yay!
Blocks?
Not here.
Oh!
This? Did you see that?
Is this it? Is this it? Looks like this.
Okay, here we go!
GO! GO!
Oops!
Ah! Stingrays!
Aaaaah!
So cute! It's started!
It's started! Wait!
We're not supposed to leave them in the batch, are we? I see!
Oh, but something...
I don't know.
It's pretty hard, isn't it?
Isn't it? What should I do with it?
Oh! The line... You mean this is here?
That makes sense!
Oh, here it is.
Hey!
Here we go!
Surprisingly heavy! It's a little heavier than I thought it would be...
You guys are doing the heavy lifting!
Okay, this is...
This is here, right?
Oh, and can we do this here?
It's gonna work! Can you do it?
Oh, but, no, no. Here?
Here. Ah!
Hurry, hurry! Come on, come on, come on! Two minutes!
Oh, I'm sorry! Oh, it's the other way! Wrong way!
That's, uh, that's wrong! This is, uh, that?
This is Minami's, maybe here.
And this one, this one.
I lost.
So..,
Isn't this the only one? Is that not it?
This one?
This is here, isn't it?
This is difficult.
It's very difficult.
I don't know, but I like this one,
Yes, it is. I don't get it.
Maybe this part is different.
This, this, this.
This is it! This is it!
That's what I'm talking about.
Go, go, go, go.
There they go.
It's gone! It's gone! It's gone!
We did it!
Yay!
Who was the third winner?
Well, he did a great job.
Is there more?
Who's the second winner?
Is there a penalty?
Oh, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Okay, let's all remember.
Okay.
Here we go.
Number 20.
Square!
It's moving!
Wait a minute!
Three!
Oh, no!Oh, no!
Wait, it moves so much.
Oh, what was that?
Oh, no!
Oh, here, here
Oh, here, here.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God, am I gonna die? Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, am I gonna die?
Oh, my God.
Uh...
Game over, right?
Yeah. - Yeah.
I'm gonna have to log out.
Oh, no, I'm gonna die?
No, I'm gonna get kicked out.
I'm gonna get kicked out.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
They've logged us out.
We're logged out.
Oh, my God.
Can we log in again?
Can we try again?
One more time, please.
Well, we've made a special arrangement so that you can log in one more time as is.
Please use the device.
Please try again.
Yes!
You'll never make a mistake again.
That's right.
Let's join forces.
Let's do it.
Here we go.
Here it is!
NAGI-chan's
Here it is.
Thank you very much.
A long one here.
The long one is here, right?
It's hard to do without a clue, isn't it?
Yes, it's difficult, isn't it?
I wonder if it's possible to do without it.
There are more and more.
Here it is.
That's it.
The footprints are too thick.
There's a hint that it's different.
Oh, really?
But it's right.
Oh, this...
I'm going to get stuck.
Yes, it's good.
I can do it.
One and a half more minutes.
Here we go. We're good.
We did it!
We did it.
I'll remember.
I'll remember
I'm in charge of remembering
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, okay.
Then, please do it.
Here we go.
Come on.
Nagi.
Ho!
Ho.
Aah!
Oh, shit.
It's okay.
Oh, no, not at all.
Stop moving.
Wasn't there a triangle?
There wasn't.
It moves so much!
I don't know what to do!
I touched it!
Who's that?
I think it's me.
That's what I'm talking about!
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, oh, is that it? Maybe that's it.
Uh-uh.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
Oh, there we go.
There it is.
Oh, and...
Oh, no.
Oh, here it comes.
Oh, where was it? Around here?
Oh, no!
Oh, shit!
Oh, is that it?
Oh, my God!
Oh, no!
Oh, no! Whose is this?
It's hard! It's hard!
Oh, no!
No! No!
No!
Ehhhhhh!
Oh, the drop.
Suddenly it's getting cold!
Oh no!
But you said you cleared 3 rooms, right?
Yes, we cleared one.
We cleared one.
I want to do it, but...
I want to clear one room.
What's the next room?
I'm sorry.
I'd like to ask you a favor.
Then, I'll make a special exception.
Let's try that room too.
Thank you!
Always a pleasure!
I can't fail for sure. I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it again.
It's the third time's the charm.
Let's go home alive.
Let's get out of here alive.
Oh, here it comes!
Of course.
Here we go!
All right!Okay!
Oh! That's great!
Yes!
What's this?
Yes, I've got it.
That's it!
I see it!
Oh, no! It's starting!
Wait a minute!
Where is it? Is that it? Is that the red one?
Oh, no, it's hard!
Wait!
Oh, no!
It's hard! Time is running out!
Aah! It's too hard!
Can you do it?
It's so hard!
Did you hit it?
No!
Come on!
Did I hit it?
Sorry, Mika!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
Aah! It's not hitting at all!
Hey!
It's so hard!
Sorry!
Time is running out.
It's just time.
I'm losing time!
Hey, one step apart...
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
My eyes, my eyes, my eyes... they're not working at all.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What?
Baseball.
Oh, no!
It was baked oil.
It's burning oil.
It's the final blow.
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Huh?
What?
You're kidding? I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
They're going to eat me.
What?
Are we done? We did it already? Just now.
Did we do it?
What?
I don't really remember.
I miss it.
What?
Please get out of here.
It's hard.
It's difficult.
One more time.
Can I have one more chance?
Okay, one last try.
Oh, I'm sorry.
One more chance.
Try this one for the prawns.
Yes, sir.
Okay, then.
Let's go.
Oh, this one.
Let's reach out.
Yes, sir.
Yes, of course.
Don't practice.
Hey!
Not even close.
Hey, hey!
Oh, no!
Hey!
Open your mouth!
Open up!
Open it!
Too close!
Hey!
Please!
You guessed it!
Hey!
Yes, we're back in the real world. That was fun! It was fun!
I didn't get through it, but you know, I've never seen the anime, but I know the name, but it was a lot of fun,
I had a lot of fun, and the two of them knew a lot about it, which made it even more exciting. I'm glad!
I couldn't clear it, but that's why I want to come back next time.
I want to go back! Hey! You like Nogami, don't you?
I know the enemies and the rooms, and people who like them get really excited,
It's simply fun! It's fun! I think I was sweating a lot because I was having so much fun.
Hey! I was sweating! My sister was so excited!
You were so cute! I swear! It was fun!
It was so much fun to be in a party with 3 other people instead of just one, and to be able to say "I'm going to do my best" and move forward together,
I want to go again! I want to go again!
Subscribe to our channel! High rating! Please subscribe!
Please do!